&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：Webpack是否附带此webpack-bundle-analyzer，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Is Webpack comes
with this webpack-bundle-analyzer,
这有效地做到了它在罐头上说的话，对吗？
which does effectively what
it says on the tin, right?
它会分析你的包裹。
It analyzes your bundles.
你说，太好了，这是什么意思？
You're like, great, what does that mean?
快到了。
Getting there.
所以我要继续，我要翻转这个。
So I'm gonna go ahead, and
I'm just going to flip this.
开始了，很酷。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：那么，
It's on, very cool.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So,
我们要做的就是为生产而建造。
what we'll do is we're gonna build for
production.
让我们做一个NPM运行构建，这将做的是它将构建我的文件。
Let's do a npm run build, and
what this will do is it'll build my file.
它将启动包分析器，我们可以看到我的包的内容。
And it'll fire up the bundle analyzer,
and we can see the contents of my bundle.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：请稍等。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Give it a second.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：就是这样。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: This is it.
这是我的包，main.一些checksum.bundle.js，
This is my bundle,
main.some checksum.bundle.js,
它对于可视化所有代码的位置非常有用。
and it's really useful for
visualizing where all your code is.
比如什么占据了大部分的捆绑？
Like what is taking up
most of that bundle?
这是我在这里写的代码，
So this is the code I wrote over here,
源目录中的这个小片段。
this tiny little sliver
in the source directory.
我已经写了，有效地，在gzip压缩后，2.26千字节。
I have written, effectively,
after it's been gzipped, 2.26 kilobytes.
但我会运送所有这些代码，我会运送所有的洛达什。
But I am shipping all of this code,
and I'm shipping all of lodash.
我正在运送codemirror，这显然是一个很大的捆绑包。
I'm shipping codemirror,
which is clearly a large bundle.
当你这样看的时候，很明显谁是罪魁祸首。
Makes it very obvious who the culprits
are when you get to see it like this.
反应，我可能摆脱不了那个。
React-dom, I'm probably not
gonna get away from that one.
还有其他几个库，用户可以得到所有这些，对吗？
And a few other libraries, and
the user is getting all of this, right?
他们正在解析所有的信息。
They're parsing all of it.
都要通过管道，对吧？
It's all going through the tubes, right?
我不知道他们是否需要所有这些，就像我不能给他们寄一些东西一样。
I don't know if they need all of this,
like I can not send them some stuff.
比如如果他们需要代码编辑器，我们会给他们发送代码编辑器。
Like if they need the code editor,
we'll send them the code editor.